Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Political File, 1924-1953 (Box 99-471)
  - 1948
    - Subject file
      - Convention arrangements
        - Philadelphia, Pa., file
        - Platform
        - Polls
        - Post convention
        - Solbert opinion, guidance
        - Telephone
        - Tickets
      - Correspondence
        - A-M, (3 folders)
        - Mc-W, (2 folders) (Box 230)
      - Delegates, (2 folders)
        - Alphabetical list, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 231)
        - Certified delegates
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Key people
        - Letters answered
        - Lists (Box 232)
        - Positions
        - Western trip, (2 folders)
          - Airlines
          - Iowa
          - Lincoln Week
          - St. Louis, Mo.
          - Nebraska
      - Guylay, L. Richard
      - Hamilton, John D. M.
      - Hollister, John B.
      - Hoopingarner, A. A.
      - Ingalls, David S.
      - Marshall, John (Box 233)
      - Martin, I. Jack
      - McAdams, William
      - Printed matter
        - Background material, (3 folders); (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 234, Box 235)
        - Paper clippings
        - Banners
        - Booklet, The Strongest Republican Candidate
        - Cartoons, (14 folders)
        - Clip sheet
        - Clippings
          - Dewey, Thomas E.
          - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
          - General
          - MacArthur, Douglas
          - Stassen, Harold (Box 236)
          - Taft
          - Truman, Harry A.
          - Vandenberg, Arthur
          - Wallace, Henry Agard
        - Confetti, streamers, whistles, etc.
        - Decorating hotel
        - Delegate information
        - Factual information
        - Gallup Poll, candidate standing
        - Newspaper ads
        - Printing costs
        - Requests completed
        - Republican National Convention, Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 237)
        - Reprints
        - Statistics
        - Taft's schedule
      - Publicity
        - Expenditures
        - General, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 238)
        - Miscellaneous
        - Publications
      - Publicity and speech material
        - All candidates
        - Applications
        - Brown, Clarence J., statement
        - Credo
        - Democratic speeches
        - Education and federal aid
        - European Recovery Plan
        - Farm policy
        - Foreign affairs
        - Heffelfinger Agency (Box 239)
        - Hoopingarner, A. A.
        - Katz, Benjamin
        - Korb, T. W., Hornishfeger Corp., Milwaukee, Wis.
        - Letters to editors
        - Maine
        - Marshall Plan
        - National defense
        - Newspaper correspondence
        - Ohio primary contest, miscellaneous speeches, notes, etc.
        - Radio material
        - Railroad pamphlet
        - Schedules, mailing
        - Tabulations
        - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 240)
        - Taft, Martha Bowers, biography
        - Taft, The Story of Bob
        - Taxing and spending
      - Reece, B. Carroll
      - Reeves, Mildred
      - Reports and memoranda, (4 folders)
      - Reports and states (Box 241)
        - Alabama-Kentucky
        - Maine-Missouri
        - New Hampshire-Pennsylvania
        - Rhode Island-Wyoming
      - Sage, Dewitt L.
      - Tate, Benjamin E.
      - Walter, Paul W.
  - 1950 (Box 242)
    - Ohio counties
      - Adams
      - Allen
      - Ashland
      - Ashtabala
      - Athens
      - Auglaize (Box 243)
      - Belmont, (2 folders)
      - Brown
      - Butler, (2 folders)
      - Carroll (Box 244)
      - Champaign
      - Clark, (2 folders)
      - Clermont
      - Clinton
      - Columbiana, (2 folders) (Box 245)
      - Coshocton
      - Crawford
        - General
        - Precinct workers
      - Cuyahoga
        - General correspondence
          - A
          - B-G, (4 folders) (Box 246)
          - H-S, (6 folders) (Box 247)
          - T-Z, (2 folders) (Box 248)
          - Engagements
          - General, (2 folders)
      - Drake, (1 folder) (Box 249)
      - Defiance
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Delaware
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Erie
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Fairfield
      - Fayette
      - Franklin (Box 250)
        - General correspondence
          - A-H, (5 folders)
          - I-Z, (6 folders) (Box 251)
        - Engagements
        - General (Box 252)
      - Fulton
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Gallia
      - Geauga
      - Greene
      - Guernsey (Box 253)
      - Hamilton
        - General correspondence
          - A-L, (4 folders)
          - M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 254)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Hancock (Box 255)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Hardin
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Harrison
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Henry
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Highland
      - Hocking
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Holmes (Box 256)
      - Huron
      - Jackson
      - Jefferson, (2 folders)
      - Knox
      - Lake (Box 257)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Lawrence
      - Licking
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Logan
      - Lorain
        - General correspondence, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 258)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Lucas
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
        - Engagements (Box 259)
        - General, (3 folders)
      - Madison
      - Mahoning
        - Engagements
        - General, (2 folders)
      - Marion, (2 folders) (Box 260)
      - Medina
      - Meigs
      - Mercer
      - Miami
      - Monroe (Box 261)
      - Montgomery
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
        - General, (2 folders)
      - Morgan (Box 262)
      - Morrow
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Muskingum
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Noble
      - Ottawa (Box 263)
        - General
        - Precinct workers
      - Paulding
      - Perry
      - Pickaway
      - Pike
      - Portage
      - Preble (Box 264)
      - Putnam
      - Richland, (2 folders)
      - Ross
      - Sandusky
        - General
        - Engagements (Box 265)
      - Scioto, (2 folders)
      - Seneca, (2 folders)
      - Shelby
      - Stark
        - General correspondence
          - A-G
          - H-Z, (2 folders) (Box 266)
        - Engagements
        - General, (2 folders)
      - Summit
        - General correspondence
          - A-G
          - H-Z, (2 folders) (Box 267)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Trumbull
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Tuscarawas, (2 folders) (Box 268)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Union, (2 folders)
      - Van Wert
      - Vinton
      - Warren
      - Washington (Box 269)
        - Engagements
        - General
      - Wayne, (2 folders)
        - Precinct workers
        - General
      - Williams
      - Woods
      - Wyandot
        - General
        - Precinct workers
    - Subject file (Box 270)
      - Absentee voters
      - American Forestry Association
      - Athens Messenger
      - Autumn trip, (2 folders)
      - Background material
        - General, (3 folders); (11 folders) (Box 271-272)
        - Clippings, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 273, Box 274)
        - County chairman
        - Duross releases
        - Farmers
        - Immediate action
        - Johnston, Victor A.
        - Lists, (2 folders) (Box 275)
        - Literature
        - Newspaper clippings, (3 folders)
        - Printed matter, (2 folders) (Box 276)
        - Proceeding of CIO convention
        - “Radio Reports, Inc.”, (4 folders)
          - Mar.-Aug.
          - Sept.-Nov., (4 folders) (Box 277)
        - Republican Party
        - Schedule, (2 folders)
        - Taft notes
      - Ballot (Box 278)
      - Barnes, Earl
      - Baumhart, A. D.
      - Beckman, James W.
      - Bender, George
      - Biographical material
      - Bliss, Ray
      - Brannan Plan
      - British elections
      - Broadcast
      - Bryan Times
      - Buckeye Bulletin
      - Buckeye Labor News
      - Canton Repository
      - Cards
      - Carman, Esther
      - Carr, Eugene, (2 folders) (Box 279)
      - Catholic
      - Census-Ohio
      - Certificate of election
      - Chicago Journal of Commerce
      - Church statement
      - Civil rights voting records, 1949
      - Colored
      - Comstock, Boyd
      - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO)
        - General
        - Political Action Committee, (2 folders) (Box 280)
      - Congratulations
      - Contributions
        - A-B, (3 folders)
        - B-E, (6 folders) (Box 281)
        - F-H, (6 folders) (Box 282)
        - H-L, (7 folders) (Box 283)
        - L-N, (6 folders) (Box 284)
        - O-S, (6 folders) (Box 285)
        - S-T, (5 folders) (Box 286)
        - U-Z, (7 folders) (Box 287)
      - Correspondence (Box 288)
        - A-C, (7 folders)
        - D-H, (6 folders) (Box 289)
        - H-M, (7 folders) (Box 290)
        - Mc-S, (6 folders) (Box 291)
        - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box 292)
        - Miscellaneous, (3 folders); (8 folders) (Box 293)
      - Daily Tribune (Box 294)
      - Dangers of government spending
      - Daniel's article on Korea
      - Dargusch, Carlton S.
      - Dentists
      - Doctors
      - Druggists
      - Education in the Congress
      - Elyria Republican Women's Club, Elyria, Ohio
      - Emanuel, Victor, (2 folders) (Box 295)
      - Expenditures
      - Farm pamphlet
      - Farm, rural mailbox mailing
      - Ferguson, Joseph
      - Finances
      - Foreign policy
      - Formosa (Box 296)
      - Funeral directors
      - Girl's Nation release
      - Government controls
      - Governmental news
      - Gradison, Willis
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Trip résumés
      - Guylay, L. Richard, (2 folders)
      - Health (Box 297)
      - Henderson, Will
      - Housing pamphlet
      - Ingalls, David
      - International Rescue and First Aid Association Convention
      - Investigation material
        - General, (4 folders); (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 298, Box 299, Box 300)
        - Catholic
        - Chronicle weekly, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 301)
        - Clippings, (5 folders); (7 folders) (Box 302)
        - Congress of Industrial Organization News, (3 folders) (Box 303)
        - Cross, examination
        - Ferguson literature
        - Handbills
        - Institutional advertising (Box 304)
        - Labor threats
        - Letters from union men, (2 folders)
        - Lewis, John L.
        - Lists of exhibits
        - Literature
        - Machinist Weekly, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 305)
        - National Independent Labor Journal, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 306)
        - Ohio
          - Election laws
          - General
        - Photostats
        - Senate committee
        - Speakers handbook
        - Subcommittee, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 307)
        - Toward Consensus on McCarthyism
        - Union money spent
      - Invitations
      - Israel
      - Jewish statements
      - Labor
      - Latin America
      - Leech series
      - Liberty Against Socialism the Issue in Pamphlet
      - Lincoln Republican (MacIntyre)
      - Lists, (1 folder) (Box 308)
      - Literature, (2 folders)
      - Marshall, John (Box 309)
      - Martin, I. Jack
      - Military aid program
      - Minimum wage
      - National defense program
      - National security
      - Negroes
      - New Republican
      - Newsletter
      - Office of Price Administration
      - Ohio Farmer (Box 310)
      - Ohio Men of Science
      - Ohio State Journal
      - Ohio State University newsletter article
      - Organization staff
      - Oxford Press Mid Century Supplement Statement
      - Party of American Principles
      - Pearson, Drew
      - Pensions
      - Petitions
      - Pharmacists
      - Pichel, Chauncey, speech for Korean Crisis
      - Point Four
      - Polio
      - Polish pamphlet
      - Postal record statement
      - Posters
      - Principles of the Republican Party (Box 311)
      - Public Affairs Forum statement
      - Public relations, Ohio
      - Publicity mailings
      - Radio
      - Railroaders
      - Railroad labor
      - Railroadmen
      - Reader's Digest
      - Reciprocal trade
      - Remington Rand
      - Red Cross statement
      - Registration
      - Renner, Gordon (Box 312)
      - Rent control
      - Reorganization plans
      - Republican National Committee materials
      - Republican policy statement
      - Republican program for business
      - Republican Recorder
      - Requests
      - Reynolds, Howard
      - Riesel, Victor
      - Robinson, Evermont
      - Rotogravure
      - Save the Children Federation
      - Schedules and itinerary, (1 folder); (5 folders); (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 313, Box 314, Box 315)
      - Schorr, Ed D., 1949-1950
      - Science Foundation
      - Senate Week in Review, (2 folders)
      - Seheca County, Ohio, fair program
      - Social welfare
      - Speakers
      - State Labor News (Box 316)
      - State of the Union
      - Statement on O'Mahoney Report on steel
      - Statement, socialized medicine
      - Strikes
      - Story of Bob Taft
      - Students
      - Suggestions
      - Taft-Hartley Act, (2 folders)
      - Taft, form letters
      - Taft's stand on various matters
      - Taxes
      - Trips (Box 317)
      - Union Baptist Church, Cincinnati, Ohio
      - Unions in Ohio
      - University of Toledo, Toledo, Ohio
      - Veterans, (3 folders)
      - Vintherite
      - Vote statistics, (7 folders) (Box 318)
      - Walter, Paul W., (2 folders) (Box 319)
      - Warner, Milo
      - Water and power
      - Welfare
      - “What's Ahead for Business”, Commercial and Financial Chronicle
      - Wittenberg, College, Wittenberg, Ohio
      - “Why Senator Taft Should be Reelected”
      - World Scope Encyclopedia
      - Young Republicans clubs, (2 folders)
      - Young Republican News
      - Yugoslavia
  - 1952 (Box 320)
    - State file
      - Alabama
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
        - Clubs
        - Congratulatory
        - Lists
        - State officers
        - Taft supporters
      - Alaska
        - General correspondence, A-Z
        - Delegates and alternatives lists (Box 321)
        - Officers, Republicans State Central Committee
      - Arizona
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Delegates and alternatives lists
        - Form letters
        - Key men
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters
        - Thank you
        - Miscellaneous
      - Arkansas (Box 322)
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Congratulatory
        - Delegates and alternatives
        - Supporters
      - California
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (2 folders)
          - B-C, (5 folders) (Box 323)
          - C-F, (5 folders) (Box 324)
          - F-H, (5 folders) (Box 325)
          - I-M, (6 folders) (Box 326)
          - M-P, (5 folders) (Box 327)
          - R-S, (5 folders) (Box 328)
          - T-Z, (6 folders) (Box 329)
        - Clubs and delegates lists (Box 330)
        - Congratulatory
        - Emerson, Ewing
        - Millsap letters
        - Political survey
        - Questionnaires, (2 folders)
        - Supporters
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 331)
      - Canada
      - Canal Zone
      - Colorado
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
        - Congratulatory (Box 332)
        - Delegates and county chairmen
        - Supporters
        - Miscellaneous
      - Connecticut
        - General correspondence
          - A-L, (4 folders)
          - M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 333)
        - Congratulatory
        - Colleges and clubs
        - Correspondence
        - Kellems, Vivien
        - Supporters of Taft and delegates
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters
      - Delaware (Box 334)
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Delegates information
        - Form letters
        - Thank you letters
        - Young Republican
      - District of Columbia
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (2 folders); (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 335, Box 336)
        - Lists
        - Questionnaires
        - Reeves, Mildred
      - England
      - Florida
        - General correspondence
          - A-C, (3 folders)
          - E-O, (6 folders) (Box 337)
          - P-Z, (5 folders) (Box 338)
        - Colleges and clubs
        - Congratulatory
        - Delegates lists
        - Foreign (Box 339)
        - General
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters and address list
        - Survey
      - Georgia
        - General correspondence
          - A-L, (2 folders)
          - M-Z, (3 folders) (Box 340)
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Delegates list and survey
        - Supporters
      - Germany
      - Hawaii
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Delegates and officers, State Central Committee
      - Idaho
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (2 folders)
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Delegates list
        - Questionnaires
      - Illinois (Box 341)
        - General correspondence
          - A-C, (5 folders)
          - D-H, (6 folders) (Box 342)
          - I-Mc, (6 folders) (Box 343)
          - N-S, (5 folders) (Box 344)
          - S-Z, (6 folders) (Box 345)
        - Brief of Regular Republican Organization of Texas
        - Clubs and colleges (Box 346)
        - Congratulatory
        - Contribution received and survey
        - Convention plans
        - Correspondence, (3 folders)
        - Credentials
        - Delegates (Box 347)
          - General
          - Lists
        - Klein, Julius
        - Lists and addresses
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters
        - Thank-you letters after trip (Box 348)
      - Indiana
        - General correspondence
          - A-G, (6 folders)
          - H-S, (6 folders) (Box 349)
          - T-Z, (3 folders) (Box 350)
        - Colleges and club
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence, (2 folders)
        - Credentials
        - Delegates (Box 351)
        - Speech
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Young Republicans
      - Iowa
        - General correspondence
          - A-K, (4 folders)
          - L-Z, (5 folders) (Box 352)
        - Batt Bates and Jean Murray
        - Clubs and college
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates list
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft (Box 353)
        - Survey
      - Kansas
        - General correspondence
          - A-N, (4 folders)
          - O-Y, (5 folders) (Box 354)
        - Colleges and clubs
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Kentucky (Box 355)
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
        - Clubs
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists and Taft Committee
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Louisiana (Box 356)
        - General correspondence, A-W, (3 folders)
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates list
        - Louisiana story
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip to Louisiana
      - Maine
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Colleges and clubs (Box 357)
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegates list
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
      - Maryland
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (5 folders)
        - Colleges and clubs (Box 358)
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegate list and Republican Party officials
        - MacArthur, Douglas
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Veterans
      - Massachusetts
        - General correspondence
          - A-C, (4 folders)
          - D-O, (8 folders) (Box 359)
          - P-Z, (5 folders) (Box 360)
        - Clubs and colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Contributions received
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists and Dentist Committee (Box 361)
        - Form letters
        - Officers, State Central Committee
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank you letters
      - Michigan
        - General correspondence
          - A-C, (3 folders)
          - D-M, (6 folders) (Box 362)
          - Mc-Z, (7 folders) (Box 363)
        - Colleges and Young Republicans (Box 364)
        - Clubs
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters
      - Minnesota (Box 365)
        - General correspondence
          - A-P, (5 folders)
          - Q-Z, (2 folders) (Box 366)
        - Clubs and colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - Dunn, Roy
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
      - Mississippi
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (2 folders)
        - Clubs and colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Missouri
        - General correspondence
          - A-B
          - C-M, (6 folders) (Box 367)
          - Mc-Z, (4 folders) (Box 368)
        - Clubs and colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - List and thank-you letters after trip
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
      - Montana (Box 369)
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (3 folders)
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Young Republican
      - Nebraska
        - General correspondence
          - A-G, (2 folders)
          - H-Z, (5 folders) (Box 370)
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Nevada (Box 371)
        - General correspondence, B-Z
        - Credentials
        - Delegates
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
      - New Hampshire
        - General correspondence
          - A-S, (4 folders)
          - T-Z (Box 372)
        - Correspondence, (2 folders)
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - Doctors, veterinarians, lawyers, and veterans
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporter of Taft
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters
      - New Jersey
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (2 folders)
          - B-H, (6 folders) (Box 373)
          - H-P, (6 folders) (Box 374)
          - R-Z, (6 folders) (Box 375)
        - Clubs and Young Republicans (Box 376)
        - Congratulatory
        - Contributions received
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - Dentists and doctors
        - Negro delegates
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
      - New Mexico
        - General correspondence, A-Z, (2 folders)
        - Clubs (Box 377)
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates
        - Supporters
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters
      - New York
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (4 folders)
          - C-E, (7 folders) (Box 378)
          - F-H, (5 folders) (Box 379)
          - I-M, (6 folders) (Box 380)